<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Success Secrets</string>
    <string name="article_title">21 Success Secrets of Self-Made Millionaires</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">by Brian Tracy</string>
    <string name="comment">Add comment</string>
    <string name="prince_o_prince">Prince O Prince</string>

    <string name="article_text">Presented by EmpowerMe!Online at http://www.empowermeonline.com.

        \n\nHello, I\'m Brian Tracy and welcome to this program. What you are about to learn can
        change your life. These ideas, insights and strategies have been the springboards to
        financial success for millions of men and women, from every walk of life. These principles
        are simple, effective and fairly easy to apply. Each of them is based on exhaustive research
        and interviews with thousands of self-made millionaires. They have been tested and proven
        over and over again, and they will work for you if you will take them and apply them in your
        own life.

        \n\nWe are living at the greatest time in all of human history. More people are becoming
        wealthy today, starting from nothing than has ever been imagined. There are more than five
        million millionaires in America, most of them self-made, and the number is growing by 15% to
        20% each year. We even have self-made ten millionaires, hundred millionaires and more than two
        hundred billionaires. We have never seen this type of rapid wealth creation in all of human
        history.

        \n\n<b>Here\'s the good news.</b> Virtually everyone starts with nothing.
        Probably 99% of all financially successful people today started off
        broke or nearly broke. The average self-made millionaire has been
        bankrupt or close to bankrupt 3.2 times. Most of them failed over and
        over again before they finally found the right opportunity that they
        were able to leverage into financial success. And what hundreds of
        thousands and millions of other people have done, you can do as
        well.

        \n\nThe iron law of human destiny is <b>the Law of Cause and Effect</b>. This
        law is simple yet very powerful. It says that <i>there is a specific effect
            for every cause. For every action, there is a reaction</i>. This law says
        that success is not an accident. Financial success is the result of doing
        certain, specific things, over and over again, until you get the effect
        that you desire.

        \n\nNature is neutral. This means that nature, the marketplace, our
        society, does not care who you are or what you are. The law simply
        says that if you do what other successful people do, you will get the
        results that other successful people get. And if you don\'t, you won\'t.
        When you learn and apply the success secrets of self-made
        millionaires in your own life, you will experience results and rewards
        far beyond anything you have ever accomplished in life up until
        now.

        \n\n<b>Here is an important point</b>. <i>Nobody is better than you and nobody is
            smarter than you</i>. Let me repeat that. Nobody is better than you and
        nobody is smarter than you. Get those thoughts out of your mind.
        One of the primary reasons for selling yourself short, for
        underachievement and lack of financial success is the conviction that
        people who are doing better than you are better than you. This is
        simply not the case.

        \n\nThe fact is that most self-made millionaires are average people with
        average educations working at average jobs and living in average
        neighbourhoods in average houses driving average cars. But they have
        found out what other financially successful people do and they have
        done the same thing over and over again until they got the same
        results. It is no miracle and it is no accident. And when you think the
        thoughts and do the things that self-made millionaires do, you will
        begin to get the same results and benefits they do. It is all up to you.

        \n\nThere are 21 secrets of success of self-made millionaires. Each of these
        is indispensable to your becoming financially independent. The
        absence of any one of these factors can, by itself, undermine and even
        destroy your chances for health, happiness and great prosperity. The
        good news is that you can learn every one of these principles by
        practice and repetition, over and over again, until they become as
        natural to you as breathing in and breathing out. Just as you have
        learned to ride a bicycle or drive a car, you can learn the secrets of
        success of self-made millionaires and apply them in your life. And
        there are no limits except the limits you place on yourself.

        \n\nNow, let us begin:</string>

    <string name="button_1">1. Dream Big Dreams</string>
    <string name="button_2">2. Develop a Clear Sense of Direction</string>
    <string name="button_3">3. See Yourself as Self-Employed</string>
    <string name="button_4">4. Do what You love to do</string>
    <string name="button_5">5. Commit to Excellence</string>
    <string name="button_6">6. Develop a Workaholic Mentality</string>
    <string name="button_7">7. Dedicate Yourself to Lifelong Learning</string>
    <string name="button_8">8. Pay Yourself First</string>
    <string name="button_9">9. Learn Every Detail of your Business</string>
    <string name="button_10">10. Dedicate Yourself to serving Others</string>
    <string name="button_11">11. Be Impeccably honest with Yourself and Others</string>
    <string name="button_12">12. Set Priorities on your Activities and concentrate Single Mindedly
                                    on One Thing at a Time</string>
    <string name="button_13">13. Develop a Reputation for Speed and Dependability</string>
    <string name="button_14">14. Be Prepared to climb from Peak to Peak in your Life and in your Career</string>
    <string name="button_15">15. Practice Self-Discipline in all Things</string>
    <string name="button_16">16. Unlock your Inborn Creativity</string>
    <string name="button_17">17. Get Around the Right People</string>
    <string name="button_18">18. Take Excellent Care of your Physical Health</string>
    <string name="button_19">19. Be Decisive and Action Oriented</string>
    <string name="button_20">20. Never consider the Possibility of Failure</string>
    <string name="button_21">21. Back Everything you do with the Twin Qualities of Persistence
                                and Determination</string>

    <string name="ss1">The first secret of self-made millionaires is simple: <b>Dream Big Dreams!</b>
        Allow yourself to dream. Allow yourself to imagine and fantasize about the kind of life you
        would like to live and the kind of money you would like to earn and have in your bank account.

        \n\nAll great men and women begin with a dream of something
        wonderful and different from what they have today. You know the
        song that says, <i>\"You have to have a dream if you want to make a dream come true.\"</i>

        \nImagine that you have no limitations on what you can be, have or do
        in life. Just for the moment, imagine that you have all the time, all the
        money, all the education, all the experience, all the friends, all the
        contacts, all the resources and everything you need to achieve
        anything you want in life. If your potential was completely
        unlimited, what kind of a life would you want to create for yourself
        and your family?

        \n\nPractice "back from the future" thinking. This is a powerful technique
        practiced by high performing men and women that has an amazing
        effect on your mind and on your behavior. Project yourself forward
        five years. Imagine that five years have passed and that your life is
        now perfect in every respect. What does it look like? What are you
        doing? Where are you working? How much money are you earning?
        How much do you have in the bank? What kind of a lifestyle do you
        have?

        \n\nCreate a vision for yourself for the long-term future. The more clear
        your vision of health, happiness and prosperity, the faster you move
        toward it and the faster it moves toward you. When you create a
        clear mental picture of where you are going in life, you become more
        positive, more motivated and more determined to make it a reality.
        You trigger your natural creativity and come up with idea after idea
        to help make your vision come true.

        \n\nYou always tend to move in the direction of your dominant dreams,
        images and visions. The very act of allowing yourself to dream big
        dreams actually raises your self-esteem and causes you to like and
        respect yourself more. It improves your self-concept and increases
        your level of self-confidence. It increases your personal level of
        self-respect and personal happiness. There is something about dreams
        and visions that is exciting and that stimulates you to do and be
        better than you ever have before.

        \n\nHere is a great question for you to ask and answer, over and over
        again: <i>\"What one thing would you dare to dream if you knew you
        could not fail?\"</i> If you were absolutely guaranteed of success in any
        one thing in life, large or small, short-term or long-term, what would
        it be? What one great thing would you dare to dream if you knew
        you could not fail?

        \n\nWhatever it is, write it down and begin imagining that you had
        achieved this one great goal already. Then, look back to where you
        are today. What would you have done to get to where you want to
        go? What steps would you have taken? What would you have
        changed in your life? What would you have gotten into or gotten out
        of? Who would you be with? Who would you no longer be with? If
        your life was perfect in every respect, what would it look like?
        Whatever it is that you would do differently, take the first step today.

        \n\nDreaming big dreams is the starting point of achieving your goal of
        financial independence. The number one reason that people never
        succeed financially is because it never occurs to them that they can do
        it. As a result, they never try. They never get started. They continue
        to go around in financial circles, spending everything they earn and a
        little bit more besides. But when you begin to dream big dreams
        about financial success, you begin to change the way you see yourself
        and your life. You begin to do different things, bit by bit, gradually,
        until the whole direction of your life changes for the better. Dreaming
        big dreams is the starting point of financial success, and becoming a
        self-made millionaire.</string>

    <string name="ss2">Secret number two, <b>develop a clear sense of direction</b>. This is where
        you take your dreams out of the air and you crystallize them into
        clear, specific written goals. Perhaps the greatest discovery in human
        history is that, <b>\"You become what you think about most of the time.\"</b>
        The two factors that determine what happens to you in life, more
        than anything else, are <i>what you think about and how you think about
        it.</i>

        \n\nSuccessful people think about their goals most of the time. As a
        result, they are continually moving toward their goals and their goals
        are moving toward them. Whatever you think about most of the time
        grows and increases in your life. If you are thinking and talking and
        visualizing your goals, you tend to accomplish far, far more than the
        average person who is usually thinking and talking about their
        worries and problems most of the time.

        \n\nHere is an exercise for you. Take a sheet of paper and write the word
        "Goals" at the top with today\'s date. Then, make a list of 10 goals that
        you would like to achieve over the next 12 months. Write your goals
        in the present tense, as though a year has passed and you have
        already achieved them. Begin each goal with the word "I" to make it
        personal to you. By making out a list of 10 goals for yourself for the
        next year, you will have moved yourself into the top 3% of adults in
        our society. The sad fact is that 97% of adults have never made a list
        of goals in their entire lives.

        \n\nOnce you have your list of 10 goals, go back over the list and ask this
        key question: <i>\"Which one goal on this list, if I were to achieve it,
        would have the greatest positive impact on my life?\"</i>

        \n\nWhatever your answer to that question, circle that goal and make
        that your number one, most important goal for the future. Set a
        deadline, make a plan, take action on your plan and do something
        every day that moves you toward your goal.
        From now on, think and talk about that goal all the time. Think and
        talk about how you can achieve that goal. Think and talk about all the
        different things that you can do to make that goal a reality. This
        exercise will stimulate your creativity, increase your energy and
        unlock your potential.
    </string>

    <string name="ss3">Success secret number three, <b>see yourself as self-employed</b>. Accept
        complete, 100% responsibility for everything you are and everything
        you will ever be. Refuse to make excuses or to blame other people for
        your problems or short comings. Stop complaining about things in
        your life that you are not happy about. Refuse to criticize other
        people for anything. You are responsible. If there is something in
        your life that you don\'t like, it is up to you to do something about it.
        But you are in charge.

        \n\nThe top 3% of Americans see themselves as self-employed, no matter
        who signs their paycheck. The biggest mistake you can ever make is
        to ever think that you work for anyone other than yourself. You are
        always self-employed. You are always the president of your own
        personal services corporation, no matter where you might be
        working at the moment. When you see yourself as self-employed,
        you develop the entrepreneur mentality, the mentality of the highly
        independent, self-responsible, self-starting individual. <b>Instead of
        waiting for things to happen, you make things happen.</b> You see
        yourself as the boss of your own life. You see yourself as completely
        in charge of your physical health, your financial well being, your
        career, your relationships, your house, your home, your car and
        every element of your existence. This is the mindset of the truly
        excellent person.

        \n\nSelf-responsible people are intensely result oriented. They take high
        levels of initiative. They volunteer for assignments and they are
        always asking for more responsibility. As a result, they become the
        most valuable and respected people in their organizations. They
        continually prepare themselves for positions of higher authority and
        responsibility in the future. You should do the same.

        \n\nHere\'s a question: <i>\"If you were president for a day in your company,
        or were completely responsible for results where you work, what one
        change would you enact immediately?\"</i> Whatever it is, write it down,
        make a plan and begin on it today. This alone could change your life.
    </string>

</resources>
