<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">21 Success Secrets of Self-made Millionaires</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">by Brian Tracy</string>
    <string name="comment">Add comment</string>
    <string name="article_text">Presented by EmpowerMe!Online at http://www.empowermeonline.com. \n\nHello, I\'m Brian Tracy and welcome to this program.
        What you are about to learn can change your life. These ideas, insights and strategies have been the springboards to financial success for millions
        of men and women, from every walk of life. These principles are simple, effective and fairly easy to apply. Each of them is based on exhaustive research
        and interviews with thousands of self-made millionaires. They have been tested and proven over and over again, and they will work for you if you will take
        them and apply them in your own life. We are living at the greatest time in all of human history. More people are becoming wealthy today, starting from nothing
        than has ever been imagined. There are more than five million millionaires in America, most of them self-made, and the number is growing by 15% to 20% each year.
        We even have self-made ten millionaires, hundred millionaires and more than two hundred billionaires. We have never seen this type of rapid
        wealth creation in all of human history.

        \n\n<b>Here\'s the good news.</b> Virtually everyone starts with nothing.
        Probably 99% of all financially successful people today started off
broke or nearly broke. The average self-made millionaire has been
bankrupt or close to bankrupt 3.2 times. Most of them failed over and
over again before they finally found the right opportunity that they
were able to leverage into financial success. And what hundreds of
thousands and millions of other people have done, you can do as
well. The iron law of human destiny is the Law of Cause and Effect. This
law is simple yet very powerful. It says that there is a specific effect
for every cause. For every action, there is a reaction. This law says
that success is not an accident. Financial success is the result of doing
certain, specific things, over and over again, until you get the effect
that you desire. Nature is neutral. This means that nature, the marketplace, our
society, does not care who you are or what you are. The law simply
says that if you do what other successful people do, you will get the
results that other successful people get. And if you don\'t, you won\'t.
When you learn and apply the success secrets of self-made
millionaires in your own life, you will experience results and rewards
far beyond anything you have ever accomplished in life up until
now.
        \n\nHere is an important point. Nobody is better than you and nobody is
smarter than you. Let me repeat that. Nobody is better than you and
nobody is smarter than you. Get those thoughts out of your mind.
One of the primary reasons for selling yourself short, for
underachievement and lack of financial success is the conviction that
people who are doing better than you are better than you. This is
simply not the case.
The fact is that most self-made millionaires are average people with
average educations working at average jobs and living in average
neighborhoods in average houses driving average cars. But they have
found out what other financially successful people do and they have
done the same thing over and over again until they got the same
results. It is no miracle and it is no accident. And when you think the
thoughts and do the things that self-made millionaires do, you will
begin to get the same results and benefits they do. It is all up to you.
There are 21 secrets of success of self-made millionaires. Each of these
is indispensable to your becoming financially independent. The
absence of any one of these factors can, by itself, undermine and even
destroy your chances for health, happiness and great prosperity. The
good news is that you can learn every one of these principles by
practice and repetition, over and over again, until they become as
natural to you as breathing in and breathing out. Just as you have
learned to ride a bicycle or drive a car, you can learn the secrets of
success of self-made millionaires and apply them in your life. And
there are no limits except the limits you place on yourself.
Now, let us begin:</string>

    <string name="article_text2">\n\n<i>The first secret of self-made millionaires is simple:</i> <b>Dream Big
Dreams!</b></string>

    <string name="article_text3">Allow yourself to dream. Allow yourself to imagine and
fantasize about the kind of life you would like to live and the kind of
money you would like to earn and have in your bank account.
All great men and women begin with a dream of something
wonderful and different from what they have today. You know the
song that says, \"You have to have a dream if you want to make a dream come true.\"
Imagine that you have no limitations on what you can be, have or do
in life. Just for the moment, imagine that you have all the time, all the
money, all the education, all the experience, all the friends, all the
contacts, all the resources and everything you need to achieve
anything you want in life. If your potential was completely
unlimited, what kind of a life would you want to create for yourself
and your family?
Practice "back from the future" thinking. This is a powerful technique
practiced by high performing men and women that has an amazing
effect on your mind and on your behavior. Project yourself forward
five years. Imagine that five years have passed and that your life is
now perfect in every respect. What does it look like? What are you
doing? Where are you working? How much money are you earning?</string>
</resources>
